Mataja Maughan

(435) 881-6027 | Layton, Utah 84041 | Matajamaughan@gmail.com
Portfolio: www.matajamaughan.com | Github: www.github.com/TajaMaughan
LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/mataja-maughan-0ab80316a/

Full Stack Web Developer seeking opportunities in React and NodeJS. Embodies a strong desire to always self-improve, using exceptional organizational and problem solving skills. Capable of taking charge in large projects to improve and achieve daily and long term goals for the company.

Technical Skills

	_	
•	Rea	a cot
•	1756	1 (J

NodeJS

Express.js

Mongo

Mongoose

MySQL

Sequelize

REST APIs

iQuery

Javascript

• HTML

• CSS

Heroku

Git

Projects

Eat the Burger | https://github.com/TajaMaughan/burger

This project utilizes a custom ORM to access a MySQL database that holds a list of burgers, and keeps track of whether is has been "devoured" or is still uneaten. It is hosted on Heroku at https://mysterious-basin-54212.herokuapp.com/.

Google Book Search | https://github.com/TajaMaughan/GoogleBooks

A project that utilizes the Google Books API to render a list of books from the user's chosen search term. Books are able to be saved to a Mongo database, then the list of saved books is able to be viewed. The front end is done in React, with a back end utilizing Node, Express, and Mongoose. The final project can be viewed at https://stark-mountain-32566.herokuapp.com/

Experience

Smith's Food & Drug Pharmacy Technician Sunset - Bountiful - Logan, Utah

April 2017 - Current, July 2013 - January 2016

- Assisted in adjusting workflow to better accomplish tasks that were time sensitive.
- Worked as part of a cohesive unit to process prescriptions and assist customers.
- Communicated with insurances to assist patients in fixing problems with their insurance.

U of U Outpatient Pharmacy

Salt Lake City, Utah

December 2015 - May 2017

Inventory Technician

- Worked as part of a team to maintain inventory in the pharmacy. Prepared daily orders and maintained organization on the shelves while putting product away.
- Assisted in determining cost effectiveness of different brands of medication. Recommended changes when necessary.
- Spearheaded project to reorganize all medications within pharmacy to better utilize space and assist with making products easier to find

Education

University of Utah - Full Stack Web Development Immersive **Bridgerland Applied Technology College** - Pharmacy Technician Program **Utah State University** - General Education